{
  "topic": "6.5",
  "title": "Дробь",
  "types": [
    {
      "id": "6.5.1",
      "title": "",
      "answer_spec": {
        "type": "string",
        "format": "ege_decimal",
        "normalize": ["strip_spaces"]
      },
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{3x - 4} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "1,4" },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x - 1} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "1,5" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x + 2} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "-1,75" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x - 3} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "3,2" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "0,25" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x - 2} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "2,2" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x - 1} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "0,625" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x + 3} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "-1,25" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x - 5} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "2,6" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x + 1} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "-0,25" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x - 4} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "4,5" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x + 5} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "-4,8" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x - 4} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "2,125" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "0,1" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x - 6} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "6,25" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x + 1} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "-0,8" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x - 3} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "1,75" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x + 4} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "-1,875" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{x - 7} = 2 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "7,5" }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.5.1.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\dfrac{1}{2x - 2} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "text": "1,1" }
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
